http://www.cbc-network.org/privacy-notice/

Making Life
Egg “Donation”
#BigFertility
Breeders: A Subclass of Women?
Updated May 1, 2018
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for The Center for Bioethics and Culture (http://www.cbc-network.org). This privacy notice applies to information collected by our websites:
The Center for Bioethics and Culture: http://www.cbc-network.org/
The Paul Ramsey Institute: http://www.ramseyinstitute.org
Breeders: A Subclass of Women?: http://breeders.cbc-network.org
Anonymous Father’s Day: http://www.anonymousfathersday.com
Eggsploitation: http://www.eggsploitation.com
It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. This information may include:
Email address
Name
Title
Telephone number
Postal or other physical address
We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. We will use your information to respond to you regarding the reason(s) you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g., to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email or by mail in the future to tell you about our work; to let you know of films, books, or other items we may create, develop, sell, or give away; to ask you for donations; or to let you know of changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via info@cbc-network.org:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, customer service or accounting) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Other
We use PayPal and Square to receive donations and take orders. Their privacy policies are located here (PayPal) and here (Square).
We may, on occasion, request information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary, and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving our work and/or the use and satisfaction of this site.
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
This policy may be updated from time to time for reasons such as operational practices or regulatory changes, so we recommend that you review our Privacy Policy when returning to our website.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, please contact us immediately at info@cbc-network.org.
ShareTweetPinShare
Search CBC-Network
Join Our Email ListVenus Rising PodcastFeature Length Documentary Films #BigFertility: It's All About The Money
Breeders: A Subclass of Women?Watch On Demand
Anonymous Father's DayWatch On Demand
Documentary Short Maggie's StoryWatch On Demand
Twitter Tweets by @cbcnetwork
More Recent PostsAre Disabled Children Worth Less?Confessions of a Serial Egg DonorMovie Review: Ghosts of the RepubliqueGive Thanks With Us!Up Close With Emmy Award Winner Barry StevensThe Center for Bioethics and Culture is a non-profit 501(c)(3) public benefit educational organization.
Categories
Article
Blog
Archives Archives
Select Month
December 2020
November 2020
October 2020
April 2003
About CBC CBC addresses bioethical issues that most profoundly affect our humanity, especially issues that arise in the lives of the most vulnerable among us.
Contact CBC
3380 VINCENT RD STE HUB
PLEASANT HILL, CA 94523-4324
925-407-2660
info@cbc-network.org
Privacy
Copyright © 2001–2020
ShareTweetPinShare
